restoreguard.com 2010-12-01

# RestoreGuard | Privacy Policy

**Cookies  
**  
Cookies are a standard Internet technology, a small text file that is put on your hard drive by the server that hosts a web page. They can’t be used to gain control of your computer or to put a virus on your computer. No one else can read our cookies, and we only use them to improve the quality of our service to you. Your Internet browser was probably originally set up to accept cookies, but you can always reset it to refuse them or to ask you each time a site tries to put one on your computer. Please note, if you don’t let us install our cookie on your computer, you can still use the website, but some parts of it might not work correctly.

**Information Collected**

Our computers collect non-personally identifiable data (your IP address, how often you visit our site, which pages you visit, etc.) each time you visit RestoreGuard.com. We use this information to make the site better – easier to use and simpler.

We will only collect personally identifiable data (your name, email address, phone number, etc.) on forms YOU complete. This information might be used for promotions, specials, or to contact you when you have a question. YOU are in complete control of what personally identifiable information you give us.

**Information Collected**

Our computers collect non-personally identifiable data (your IP address, how often you visit our site, which pages you visit, etc.) each time you visit RestoreGuard.com. We use this information to make the site better – easier to use and simpler.

We will only collect personally identifiable data (your name, email address, phone number, etc.) on forms YOU complete. This information might be used for promotions, specials, or to contact you when you have a question. YOU are in complete control of what personally identifiable information you give us.

**Security  
**  
RestoreGuard.com is as committed to the security of your computer system as we are to your privacy. We use various types of standard Internet security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure.  
**  
Changes in Privacy Policy**

RestoreGuard.com might choose to update our privacy policy occasionally. If we do, we will post a notice on the website so you can review any changes and how they might affect you. Also, please review this page from time to time to make sure you haven’t missed any such notices. By continuing to use RestoreGuard.com, you are agreeing to this privacy policy and any updates we make to it.
